# **CURRICULAM VITAE**

Siddhika Tripathi (UI Developer)

Contact No:+918076403617, 8800715903 E-mail: tripathisiddhika123@gmail.com

# **Career Objective**

A competent web designing professional with 4 year of qualitative experience in UI Development looking for a challenging new role in the IT industry with the opportunity to work with the latest technologies on diverse projects. And skills for the organizational growth and enhance my ability and experience as well.

## **Experience**

**Organization**: Sterco digitex, Noida **Post**:UI Developer **Period**:Aug 2019 -Present **Responsibilities**:

Designed websites using multiple platform including HTML,

Maintenance and up-gradation of the existing code according to new design and requirements.

& To resolve issues faced by my team i.e. other developers.

Created user interfaces for desktop browsers, tablet and mobile devices.

**Organization**: StariglobalTechnologies, Delhi **Post**: UI developer **Period**: Oct 2018 -Aug 2019 **Responsibilities**:

Designed websites using multiple platform including HTML, Wordpress

Maintenance and up-gradation of the existing code according to new design and requirements.

& To resolve issues faced by my team i.e. other developers.

& Created user interfaces for desktop browsers, tablet and mobile devices.

& Created graphics including Visiting Card, icons and Images for Online Advertisement using Photoshop and Corel Draw.

**Organization**: eweblink **Post**: Web Designer **Period**: May 2017 – Sept 2018 **Responsibilities**:

 $\slash\hspace{-0.6em}$  Designed websites using multiple platform including HTML, Wordpress.

&Created advertisement images for online marketing and Visiting cards using Corel Draw and Photoshop.

Designed User interface designs for mobile applications using Photoshop.

### Some of My Projects

Project Title: Devyani International Limited

**URL:**http://dil-rjcorp.com/

What have I done? I have completely developed this website PSD to HTML.

**Project Title:** Xebia Academy

URL: https://www.xebiaacademyglobal.com/

What have I done? I have completely developed this website PSD to HTML.

Project Title: KRmangalam

URL: https://www.krmangalam.edu.in/

What have I done? I have completely developed this website PSD to HTML.

Project Title: m2kindia

**URL:** <a href="https://www.m2kindia.com/">https://www.m2kindia.com/</a>

What have I done? I have developed this website PSD to HTML

Project Title: amp-india

URL: http://www.amp-india.com/

What have I done? I have worked on this website to make new pages.

#### Websites

- http://dil-rjcorp.com/
- https://www.xebiaacademyglobal.com/
- https://www.krmangalam.edu.in/
- https://www.m2kindia.com/
- https://www.bhavnacorp.com/
- https://pafi.in/
- https://www.srmup.in/
- http://www.amp-india.com/

#### **Educational Qualification**

- Diploma In Applied Arts From Meera bai Institute Of Technology
- Diploma In Web Designing From Young Marry Christian Association.
- Diploma In Angular From Ducat Noida
- <u>10<sup>th</sup> From C.B.S.E</u>
- 12<sup>th</sup> From C.B.S.E

## **Technical Skills**

- Full Knowledge In Html, Css, Bootstrap
- Angular js
- Full Knowledge In Corel Draw And Adobe Photoshop.
- Good Knowledge Of Notepad++, Dreamweaver, Visual Studiod
- Mobile Apps UI Designing,
- Basic Knowledge Of Ms Office
- Economic Research On Internet.

### Strength

- Honest And Hard Working.
- Good Team Player And Positive Attitude.

## Hobbies

- Travelling
- Internet Surfing.

Personal Information	
Father'sname : Mr. Arvind Kr. Tripathi	
Date of birth : 02/07/1996	
Gender : Female	
Maritalstatus : Single	
Nationality : Indian	
Language Known : Hindi, English.	
Hobbies : Netsurfing & ListeningSongs.	
I hereby declare that all the information given above is true and correct as the best of my knowledge.	
Date:	
Place: (siddhika tripa	athi)